<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
<name>GTI Resource Replicator [1.0->1.6]</name>
<author>Comrade_Alexey, LeonusDH, ✬Rustic Fox✬, Chicken Plucker</author>
<packageId>A3I.RimMods.ResourceReplicator</packageId>
<supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
	<li>1.6</li>
</supportedVersions>
<description>
Guybrush Threepwood Industries (GTI) proudly presents its premium line of matter replicators - now legally distinct from a certain Federation's food synthesizers!

Tired of mining? Tired of farming? Tired of being a Mighty Pirate who still can't afford a decent cutlass? GTI replicators downgrade the laws of thermodynamics from "law" to "friendly suggestion." Feed one a single steel bar and it hands you two back, no questions asked, no three-headed monkeys involved.

"Computer. Replicate grog. Hot." And lo, it just works.

=====

Product Catalogue
- Resource Replicator: duplicates steel, wood, plasteel, components and the other honest building blocks of empire.
- Organic Replicator: clones food, crops and meals. Also converts all meat into beef, because GTI's legal department strongly prefers not to know what the meat used to be.
- Medicinal Replicator: copies drugs and medicine, from herbal poultices to glowing ultratech wonder-juice.
- Each unit politely sips 6,000W. (The heisenberg compensators are very thirsty.)
- Requires research, filed under the "Rustic's Mods" tab.
- Free with every purchase: angry comments insisting this is overpowered.

=====

Does NOT feature
- Human cloning. We tried. The less said about the rubber chicken with a pulley in the middle, the better. GTI cannot replicate a soul, a new girlfriend, or root beer that tastes the way you remember it.

Banned on several planets for being "overpowered." We at GTI prefer the term "generously specced." Now rendered in glorious 3D SCUMM-o-Vision.

=====

Credits:

[MGW] Henry - Created Original Duplication Mod Which this one is inspired by
Chicken Plucker - Art and CoDev , for maintaining the mod during RW1.0.
Rustic Fox - CoDev, Mod Maintaining during RW1.1-1.2
Wasda - Work on the inital missing items patch
Ins0mniac - Update to 1.3, and missing items patch integration
Comrade_Alexey - Update to 1.4 and 1.5

Version: 1.8.6.11
Changelog:
1.8.6.11 - Rebranded under Guybrush Threepwood Industries; rewrote the mod, building and research descriptions with fresh flavour.
1.8.6.10 - Removed the Russian translation; this fork now ships English only.
1.8.6.9 - Guarded neurotrainer recipes with MayRequire="Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty" so they only load when Royalty is installed (no more load errors without the DLC). Renamed the 1.6 recipe file to match the version folder.
</description>
</ModMetaData>